- What's up with you?
- I've gotta tell you something.
Gustavo. nice boots.
I haven't seen you
in a couple of days.
I've been busy.
You fucking piece of shit!
(shattering)
You have the balls to come in
here after running to daddy?
Anyone else here? Gustavo?
I don't know where he is.
We have to talk.
You can't do it alone.
I'm not alone.
Does Club Glitter
mean anything to you?
Did that sister find
out we were there?
No. she met some guys and left with them.
What guys?
He kinda looked like. like.
a Latino Freddie Mercury.
- What you boys doing here?
- We just cruisin'.
Then cruise.
We sell it right here in the hood.
Same as weed.
$100.000 off a single key?
(click)
Oh. shit. (Grunts)
(gunshot)
I'm comin'. man!
They're on their way. You're
gonna be all right. (Gasping)
♪♪
(footsteps)
(dogs barking in distance)
(engine revs)
(siren wails in distance)
(indistinct conversation)
(speaking indistinctly)
just chillin'.
ANDRE: Just chillin'...
(continues indistinctly)
CISSY: Yeah. I know. I-I heard.
Um. have you seen Franklin?
Mm-hmm. Can you just...
(sighs) Just send
him home. you know?
I just... I just
need to see him.
Or he can call me or.
you know. just. uh...
All right. (receiver thuds)
(crickets chirping)
(dogs barking in distance)
(door creaking)
Where have you been?!
At the station.
(exhales sharply)
God. (Exhales)
- Mm.
- (Kisses)
(Dogs continue
barking in distance)
(both exhale)
Hope you could give
them more than I could.
Did the back and forth
there for over two hours.
You went to the hospital?
(lighter flicks)
Mm-hmm. How's Leon?
He caught two bullets. Franklin.
He's lucky to be alive.
Marla was hysterical. I
didn't have much for her.
He gonna be good. though?
Looks that way. Yeah.
(exhales sharply)
You gon' make me ask?
It's Leon. You know.
Always starting some shit.
Finally mouthed off
to the wrong person.
You know. he probably caught
him coming by the house.
So you had nothing to
do with it. right?
No.
Come on. Mom. Of course not.
You scare me. Franklin.
(breathing unevenly)
How easy it is for you
to look me in the eye
and lie your ass off.
You got your best friend's
blood on your clothes
and you don't miss
a goddamn beat.
(dog barking in distance)
Jerome was here.
Heard the news.
Wanted to check in.
Guilt was all over his face.
At least someone in this family
has still got a fucking conscience.
What'd he say?
He didn't have to say shit.
I wanna hear it from you.
What you wanna hear?
Start with how long you've been
slinging the weed for him.
Six months.
Give or take.
Six months you've been
lying to my face.
Playing me for a goddamn fool.
No. it was never easy lying to you.
(scoffs)
And I didn't like it. (chuckles)
But I had to step up. get
somethin' real going.
Ain't like you don't know
about smoking no weed.
What you say?
Who the fuck you think
you talkin' to?!
You ain't gonna fucking talk to me
this way. You... (pounding on door)
Miss Cissy?
(dogs barking in distance)
(door creaking) I. uh...
hope it's not too late.
- You doin' all right?
- Yeah. we're good.
(barking continues)
CISSY: I already talked to
a bunch of your friends.
ANDRE: Yeah. I wanted a
minute with the boy.
if you don't mind.
He's man enough to
speak for himself.
(faucet turns on. water running)
(faucet turns off)
Hey. Franklin.
Hey. relax. relax.
All right. I know you've seen
your fair share of badges today.
I was hoping you and me.
we could have a
different conversation.
It's like I told them.
man. I don't...
I don't know anything and
I didn't see anything.
What if I told you I saw two
boys parked down the street
watching your house?
Got a good look at their faces.
All I need you to do is help
me fill in some blanks.
Give me a name.
I'll take care of the rest.
Afraid I can't help you.
Excuse me.
(beads rattle)
♪♪
JULIA: And what about
the fish tank?
(mouth full) Fish tank?
Yeah. it's in the back
of the storage unit.
Remember you said you thought
fish would be soothing?
Oh. right.
Yeah. that seemed
like a good idea.
Until I realized we'd have
a vat of floating bacteria
in our living room.
Hey. I understand.
You have bigger things to worry about
than a fish tank. (Door rattles open)
Oh. shit. Uh. Jules. sorry.
Look. I gotta run.
Um. you know. why don't
you just get rid
of the fish tank if
you want. all right?
Yeah. sure. Fine.
Okay. I'll talk to you soon.
I love you.
(receiver clatters)
That's all they were
able to salvage.
(bag thuds)
Wait. what about Elena?
Her Jeep was hit.
But they got her out.
She had some burns. but nothing too bad.
(bottle cap opens)
Flew her to Soto
Cano for treatment.
(bottle cap clatters)
Then it's all destroyed?
The... the camp. the
processing tent.
our pipeline?
(gasps. sniffles)
I have other suppliers
we can use for now.
Who?
The Colombians?
It'll keep things moving.
Who are they? Escobar's people?
Escobar's too powerful.
Could run us over and
not even feel the bump.
Okay.
The Medellín Cartel controls.
like. 90% of the
Colombian coke trade.
Uh-huh. And we'll be dealing
with the other 10%.
Out of Cali.
Can they meet our needs?
At decent prices.
But there'll be a
bigger slice taken out
than getting the
leaves from Peru.
Yeah. but I guess I'm more
concerned with whether or not
we can trust them.
Oh...
Okay. Um. okay.
How soon can we sit
down with them?
(exhales) The next few days.
but it has to be just me.
Hey. trust me. I'm
doing you a favor.
(horn blares)
GUSTAVO: Pinche Pedro.
What did Ramiro say?
Well. he wasn't happy.
Obviously.
But he agreed to
keep things running.
(distant shouting) (scoffs)
He's letting it continue.
(siren wailing in distance)
(speaking Spanish)
(engine revving)
(sighs)
First. Ramiro's taking control
of the entire operation.
He's taking it away from you?
It could be a lot worse.
(chuckles softly)
Peor que being Ramiro's slave?
Hmm?
He also doesn't wanna do
business with Stomper anymore.
Those Monarcas pose
too much risk.
and we don't need them.
Once my father's gone.
we could use our own
distribution network.
And what do I tell El
Stomper and Hernan? Hmm?
You aren't to do anything.
Should be enough for
you to start over.
(exhales sharply)
You want me to run?
You killed two of his men.
He's not gonna let that go.
You're siding with him? Hmm?
(speaking Spanish)
Con mi familia. Oso.
Con mi familia.
¿Qué quieres que haga? You want
me to turn my back on them?
Run away with you?
(huffs)
Look at me.
(hits truck) Look at me. carajo.
(siren wailing)
(tires screech. siren passes)
I'm not gonna run.
And maybe we don't have to run.
(sirens wailing in distance)
(indistinct conversations)
(engine starts)
(horn honks)
(conversations continue)
(car doors closing)
(girls murmuring. giggling)
Been trying to get a minute
with you. but your pops.
you know. we have...
(girls laugh)
Ooh! (Giggling)
(giggles)
Summer classes going okay?
(chuckles) Boring as hell.
but it'll look good
on my transcripts.
(horn honks)
How's Leon?
Coming home from the
hospital today.
And you? You all right?
Cool.
(door closes) Thanks
for walking me home.
(beads rattle) My daddy
brought the hammer down.
Don't want me around
none of y'all.
So we gonna have to
roll a different way.
It's all good. though.
I know it's a little messy.
I didn't expect you
to come. so...
(beads rattling)
The... the cops.
They was on their way.
and. you know. and Leon...
I had to think fast. Mel.
I couldn't risk 'em
searching my house.
So...
you gonna risk my ass
by bringing that
shit into my crib?
I couldn't see any other way.
(exhales sharply)
I thought you was down with me.
And I thought you
actually cared about me.
But you can't see anything else
besides what's in
that fucking bag.
I'm sorry. It's not gonna happen again.
No. Franklin. just go.
Just... don't touch me. It's...
Get out. Get out of my house.
Get out.
(sighs deeply)
(knock on door)
- Hey.
- Hi.
Victoria. come in.
How's it goin'?
Okay. (Sighs) (door creaks)
How about you? Yeah. Okay.
What's goin' on?
Oh. um. actually. I
just wanted to. uh...
I just wanted to
get you something.
What is it? You know. it's to
thank you for all of your help.
No. you don't... you
don't have to do that.
It's from "Harvey."
You know. that one with the
giant invisible rabbit
that only Jimmy Stewart
can see. so...
I can't accept this.
Oh. no. I insist.
I mean. you've been the one
bright spot in all of this.
So...
Yeah. Especially when I was
throwing up everywhere
and getting punched in the face.
(laughs) Yeah.
Uh. yeah. Especially then.
(chuckles)
Listen. I just...
I can't keep doing
this for much longer.
At a certain point. I just have
to accept that she's. uh...
that she's gone. you know?
(sighs)
Hey.
You've done more than
anybody else would have.
Well. I don't know if
that's true. but...
thank you.
Can I...
Mm.
(exhales)
(exhales) Okay. I
should probably go.
Okay. (breathes sharply)
Bye.
(door creaks closed)
(inhales sharply)
(dog barking in distance)
Hey. (door closes)
Jerome ain't here.
I was looking for Franklin.
He's not here neither.
(door creaking)
(rustling)
How much you involved
in all of this?
(scoffs) Here we go.
What? You comin' for me. too?
Well. you and Jerome always
lock. step. and barrel
and everything. Okay. all right.
All right. all right. okay.
(sighs)
Look. I feel you.
Things are sideways. shit
brought into your home.
So I ain't gonna
take it personally.
but Jerome ain't here.
Franklin ain't here.
It's just me. So...
(rustling)
(purse thuds)
Here. let me get
you some coffee.
It's all falling apart.
No. it ain't.
I should've never let
him quit college.
Throwing away all the
advantages I gave him.
Nah. you was happy to
have him back home.
My brother was happy
to have him slinging.
Your brother ain't been
doing nothing but trying
to keep that boy straight.
Franklin is the one that's
been pushing ahead.
It's even been causing
some problems in our home.
so don't be blamin' Jerome.
- So I should be blaming you.
- (scoffs)
You can blame me.
Blame Jerome. you blame
Franklin for droppin' out.
But I don't see you blamin'
the one person who should be
thinkin' real hard
about her own choices.
- Excuse me?
- Look at what Franklin sees.
You kissing up to some
cracker-ass slumlord...
- You better stop. Louie.
- Begging him...
You better stop right
motherfucking there.
And thanking him for the
crumbs off the table.
Are you tryin' to take
the high road with me?
Let me remind you...
Every cent I have earned to feed him...
(lighter clicking)
to keep us alive. I have earned
standing on my own two feet.
(lighter thuds)
Not playing no small
time hustle with my man.
And definitely not laying
on my goddamn back.
(object clatters)
You better watch
your fucking mouth.
I will not stand by and watch
you try to drag my son
into that gutter your
stank ass come from.
You hear me?
I am goddamn sick and tired
of your condescending.
hypocritical. siddity
ass bullshit.
Yeah. get the fuck
up out of my house.
you Stepin Fetchit bitch.
Yeah. Yeah.
You mad Franklin' lyin'.
but you the one lyin'
to your damn self!
(door creaks)
(exhales sharply)
(Ship horn blows in
distance. bell clanging)
(horn blows in distance)
(seabirds calling)
(tool whirring)
(hammering in distance)
(door creaks)
(Ship horn blows in distance.
soft music playing)
You guys open?
Sure. Sit wherever you want.
♪♪
(door creaks open)
(hammering in distance)
(camera shutter clicks)
(hammering continues)
(men chattering)
(camera shutter clicks)
(motor rumbling)
(winding camera)
(clicking continues)
(hammering continues)
(speaking indistinctly)
(breathes sharply)
(camera shutter clicks)
You ready to order?
Oh. uh. could I get
a bowl of chowder
and a glass of water. please?
- Okay.
- Thank you.
♪♪
(hammering continues)
(men speaking indistinctly)
(object thuds loudly)
(exhales. sniffles)
Wah! Man on TV: Hyah!
Wah! Wah! Wah!
That's some weak-sauce Kato.
Kato your ass.
Wah. ah. ah!
(both make fighting noises)
Okay. you won. You won.
Show me your teeth.
Come here. show me your teeth.
Mm. y'all wanna go
get some candy?
Yes. I do. I could probably
get. like. a lollipop.
I'm gonna get me a cupcake...
What's up. man?
Hey. bring me back
some Lemonheads.
- (shouts indistinctly)
- Where your mom at?
Laying down in the back.
Hazard pay.
What about my shirt?
(TV continues indistinctly)
No. I'm just fucking with you.
You're stupid.
(sighs)
Yeah. How you feelin'?
I'm gonna need another hit
of them happy pills soon.
Then I ain't gonna hear
shit you gotta say.
(Children shouting in distance)
(groans) So break it down.
When we makin' our move?
Yeah. Workin' on it.
I mean. not for nothin'.
I could step it to a
motherfucker right now.
(chuckles) Nigga. you
can't even step.
(laughing)
Nah. for real. Like. we
gotta catch 'em in the car.
Get 'em contained like they
did Sonny in "The Godfather"
and just fuckin' kill 'em.
That is if they ridin' together.
Those two always together.
Not when they rolled up on me.
Just Lenny.
Nah. that can't be right.
Nigga. don't tell me.
I was there.
(theme music playing on TV)
(dog barking. indistinct
conversation in distance)
Man. you sure you gonna be able
to do this shit without me?
(exhales. chuckles)
I can't lie. man.
Havin' you on the
bench ain't ideal.
Well. look. it ain't about
payback. all right?
It's about rep.
You gotta let niggas know
right here. right now
that we official.
'cause if you don't.
motherfuckers are always gonna
be comin' at us. all right?
♪♪
(indistinct conversations)
(hammering) MAN: Those options...
hit or miss.
(hammering continues.
louder) Last one...
You know. you need a new
alternator. brakes.
(hammering continues) (exhales)
(Conversations
continue. indistinct)
(hammering continues. louder)
(hammering continues)
That's not... that's not
bothering you? The...
What?
♪♪
(Hammering.
conversation continues)
(bills rustling)
(pats table)
(camera shutter clicks)
(exhales)
(door creaks)
(door closes)
(exhales. breathes sharply)
(glasses clink)
(exhales)
(sighs)
Louie! (tv playing. door closes)
- Hey. Louie?
- I'm here.
Where you been? What do you
mean. where have I been?
- You know where I've been.
- (Chuckles) Stop.
Your sister came here
lookin' for you.
Almost made me whup her ass.
- Hmm.
- How'd it go?
How did it go? Huh?
How'd it go? (Laughs)
All of this in one day?
I ain't never seen
nothin' like it.
I-I upped the money to dimes.
They still came back for more.
They kept comin' back. Anyway...
What?
(dog barking in distance)
This gonna be huge.
Is somethin' wrong with that?
No. it's... (scoffs)
- It's fantastic.
- Yeah.
We about to do this shit.
(laughs)
Yeah. baby.
We gonna do this here.
We gonna do this.
Yeah.
(exhales)
(r&b music playing)
(lowered voice) I got
some VIPs comin' tonight.
- You Wanna sit with them?
- Okay.
Good.
Hey. what's
happening. candy man?
Your timing couldn't be better.
This here is Shayla.
She's one of my
newest prospects.
Don't let the baby
face fool you.
She's a prodigy. I
need to talk to you.
♪♪
This the VIP list for tonight.
A.C. Green's comin'.
Keep them girls off of him.
And get this sad brother some Henney.
Goddamn.
I want you to go upstairs.
try on them size 7 shoes.
Let me know what you think.
Okay.
All right? Right here.
(kisses)
Bam.
♪ Oh. but what they don't
understand now. baby ♪
Well. I'm glad to see
you in one piece.
You heard?
Just rumors.
Variations on a theme.
One of them had you taking
a bullet to the face.
which I am delighted
to see ain't true.
♪♪
(door closes)
Leon caught the bullet.
But he gonna be all right.
That that little nigga who
called me a busted old bitch?
Came to ask a favor. Claudia.
I need you to get
word to Ray-Ray.
Arrange a sit-down.
A sit-down? Uh-huh.
Boy. you've been watching
too many TV shows.
I don't claim to know everything
about this. uh. game.
but I'm pretty sure if a
nigga wanted you dead.
the quickest way to
expedite that shit
is to sit down in front of him.
Yeah. I'm trying to avoid that.
And you wanna use my valuable
time and resources. is that it?
Listen. if it's about product.
I could do way better now.
It ain't about that now.
You asking me to be the
United fucking Nations.
And I'm saying
I need something a
little more personal.
(engine turns off)
(helicopter blades
whirring. passing)
Hey.
You're late.
They'll front 50 kilos.
Prices are much better if
we pick it up in México.
fly it in ourselves.
That's cool.
Uh. so long as it's not
the middle of the desert.
I can live with that.
(gate rattles)
That's it? (Chuckles)
You're not gonna pull some shit?
Demand to know everything?
Ask me a million questions?
Thank you for handling that.
So. uh. listen. I talked to
the doctors at Soto Cano.
and they said that they
don't have the facilities
to treat some of
Elena's injuries.
So I had her flown to the Dallas
Burn Clinic. (Clip clicks)
Burn Clinic? She said
it wasn't that bad.
(clip clicks) It's her left
arm and a part of her leg.
It's just precautions.
So I took care of the
immigration paperwork.
and. uh. she should
be there by tonight.
So... (pounding on door)
(breathing sharply)
(speaks Spanish)
Uh. this better not be
about more late payments.
I told you we would find other
buyers if it happened again.
No. no. no. no. We
have the money.
This is my father. Ramiro.
Reed and Alejandro.
Okay. no. no. Why is he here?
Where's Gustavo?
My father's running things now.
Wanted to meet our suppliers.
We're gonna increase our
buy soon if that. uh.
helps to ease your mind.
Consistency and
routine ease my mind.
Unexpected changes don't.
Uh... (chuckles)
- Increase by how much?
- 25 kilos this time.
And we're gonna
double it soon after.
From this point forward. my son
handles all the transactions.
so please continue to treat
him with the proper respect.
(alejandro inhales. exhales)
Of course.
We just wanna do good business.
Perfect.
You're in good hands.
I look forward to a long
and prosperous
relationship here.
Well. if you gentlemen
want to come this way.
I'll get you the product.
♪♪
(man singing in Spanish)
One deal and you back out?
(speaking Spanish)
(whistles)
(footsteps approach)
(bottles clink.
bottle cap opens)
(breathes sharply)
You see. here's the thing.
I don't think it's gonna
go down like that.
I think you're gonna come here
with the cocaine
like we agreed.
It's not my choice. vato.
Not my choice.
So your girl fucks us...
and then sends you
to deliver the news?
(speaks Spanish)
She didn't send me.
I'm being cut out. too.
(laughing)
Well. ain't this some shit?
(laughs)
Look...
Hernan vouched for me.
(speaks Spanish)
Be straight with you.
Tell me. why did she
change her mind so fast?
She was on her own. pero now.
(speaks Spanish) pinche
familia's involved.
♪♪
You're telling me the
Villanueva family
is going to be my competition?
(slaps back)
You did the right thing by
coming here and telling us.
That was smart. Honest.
You know everything about
that bitch and her family?
Where they live? What
kind of people they got?
All that shit?
(speaks Spanish)
♪♪
Guess I know why you ready
for Jerome to leave.
Mm. That's the only way Claudia
will help me set up the meet.
And I told her. I won't put
you in any kind of danger
or anything... It
ain't like that.
I know.
I didn't get that at first.
She told you about us?
Way back when?
Not so much.
So you just came here
to ask me to fuck
that crazy bitch?
Nah. of course not. Mnh.
I just couldn't see
any other way...
Relax. It ain't that bad.
I just wanna be clear on exactly
what is gonna come of it.
Lenny the one out of pocket.
And it make sense after
what we did to him.
If I could just Ray-Ray
into a room...
(laughs) Oh. honey. That
is not what I meant.
Nah. I got all the
faith in the world
that you gon' handle this shit.
My question is. when
it do work out.
what's in it for me?
How much you want?
It ain't about the money.
It's about Claudia.
about that club.
If I do this. you
gon' get it for me.
(chuckles) Mm-hmm.
♪♪
RAMIRO: These numbers look good.
You know. once this ramps
up. it's gonna happen fast.
More people. more weapons.
Then we'll bring in someone
to look at the books.
I don't need any
help with the books.
I know.
You get into cocaine.
could get violent.
God forbid if anything
should happen to you.
I can't have you be the only one
that knows about our finances.
(pager beeping)
(beeping stops)
What?
It's your father's house number.
(curtains open)
(breathes sharply)
TEDDY: Hello. I'm
not in right now.
Please leave your message
after the beep. (Beep)
(machine clicks) VICTORIA: Hi. Reed.
It's Victoria calling.
I-I think I found something
that might possibly help us.
So if you could just call
me back when you get this.
I wanna share it with you.
You know. you've been so
helpful with everything.
you know. getting in a fist
fight and you throwing up...
Hello. hey. it's me. Oh. hi.
I think I found a lead.
Yeah. what'd you find?
So I was packing
up Kristin's stuff
to take back home.
including her pictures.
and that's when I started
thinking about photos.
And I remembered seeing
someone taking photos
at the club the other night.
And so I went back to Glitter
and they put me in contact
with Rinaldi. who
was there the night
that Kristin went missing.
How you doing?
And he had all these photos.
so show him the one.
(projector clicking)
That's them! Leaving the club.
(laughs)
(click) Go to the next one.
And that's Jess. right?
And him. you know.
Latin Freddie Mercury.
(click) Wait. zoom in.
Yeah. He's the one.
He's the answer to all this.
(clicking continues)
(indistinct conversations)
MAN ON SPEAKER: Order 75. double
cheeseburger and onion rings.
75. double cheeseburger
and onion rings.
- MAN: That cool?
- WOMAN: Yeah. that's cool.
(indistinct conversations)
You want some food? You hungry?
Milkshakes are good.
Nah. I'm good.
Claudia lay it all out?
(sniffs)
She laid it out.
What the hell you thought
was gonna happen?
Beat down my homie?
You fuck up his house?
You see that?
I got beat down first.
And I wasn't the one
who did it to him.
Yeah. well. we took care
of them HTB arcade niggas.
What about the cops?
You take care of them. too?
You know. matter of fact.
my next door neighbor's a cop.
Said he saw two guys
scopin' out my place.
And he's tracking
them down right now.
(scoffs)
That's how it's going down?
You a snitch. motherfucker?
(scoffs)
If you're looking for
some type of truce.
you're in the wrong place.
No. no. no. no.
No truce.
♪♪
Then what the fuck
is we doin' here?
We're gonna talk business.
Because that's what
it's about. right?
Money?
SOLOMON BURKE: ♪ Well.
you better listen
♪ My sisters and brothers
♪ 'Cause if you
do you can hear ♪
♪ There are voices still
calling across the years ♪
♪ And they're all crying
across the ocean ♪
♪ And they're cryin'
across the land ♪
♪ And they will till
we all (exhales)
♪ Come to understand
♪ None of us are free
♪ None of us are free.
one of us are chained ♪
♪ None of us are free
♪ And there are people
still in darkness ♪
♪ And they just can't
see the light ♪
♪ If you don't say it's wrong
then that says it's right ♪
♪ We got try to feel
for each other ♪
♪ Let our brothers
know that we care ♪
♪ Got to get the message.
send it out loud and clear ♪
♪ None of us are free
♪ None of us are free.
one of us are chained ♪
♪ None of us are free
♪ It's a single
truth we all need ♪
♪ Just to hear and to see
♪ None of us are free.
none of us are free ♪
♪ Oh. Lord. none
of us are free ♪
♪ Now I swear your salvation
♪ Isn't too hard to find
♪ None of us can
find it on our own ♪
♪ On our own
♪ We got to join together
♪ In spirit. heart. and mind
♪ So that every soul
who's suffering ♪
♪ Will know that
we're not alone ♪
♪ Whoa. none of us are free
♪ None of us are free. y'all
♪ None of us are free
♪ And one of are chained.
none of us are free ♪
♪ Oh. my. my. my ♪
None of us are free
♪ My. my Lord
♪ None of us are free
♪ One of us is chained.
none of us are free ♪
♪ None of us. none of us.
♪ None of us are free
♪ One of us is chained.
none of us are free ♪
♪ None of us are free
♪ None of us are free. no
♪ If one of us is chained.
none of us are free ♪
♪ Oh. Lord
♪ None of us are free
♪ If one of us is chained.
none of us are free ♪
♪♪
Captions by VITA...